<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<response><error><![CDATA[OK]]></error><limit>1</limit><offset>0</offset><number_of_page_results>1</number_of_page_results><number_of_total_results>1</number_of_total_results><status_code>1</status_code><results><aliases/><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/character/3005-421/]]></api_detail_url><birthday/><date_added>2008-06-12 16:59:07</date_added><date_last_updated>2012-10-19 11:34:38</date_last_updated><deck><![CDATA[An enigmatic character of disturbing power, the inhuman G-Man represents an unknown, trans-dimensional organization, and is a major influence on the events in the Half-Life universe.]]></deck><description><![CDATA[<h2>The Mystery Man<br/></h2> <figure data-align="right" data-embed-type="image" data-img-src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/0/6153/328232-05.jpg" data-ref-id="1300-328232" data-resize-url="" data-resized="" data-size="small"><a href="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/0/6153/328232-05.jpg" data-ref-id="1300-328232"><img src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_small/0/6153/328232-05.jpg"></a><figcaption>Close-up from the intro of Half-Life 2</figcaption></figure> Encountered for the first time in the original <a data-ref-id="3030-2980" href="/half-life/3030-2980/" slug="half-life">                                Half-Life</a>, the G-Man is an iconic character in <a data-ref-id="3010-1374" href="/valve-corporation/3010-1374/" slug="valve-corporation">                                Valve's</a> award winning franchise, manipulating events from the shadows and rarely taking direct action himself. A being of what seems to be considerable power, his true nature and origin are unknown. Throughout the first and second Half-Life games, the G-Man can be seen speaking with other characters and observing the protagonist <a data-ref-id="3005-341" href="/gordon-freeman/3005-341/" slug="gordon-freeman">                                Gordon Freeman</a> in action, watching from behind bullet-proof glass and impassable obstacles, eventually judging Gordon a useful individual worthy of recruitment into the G-Man's mysterious, unknown organization. It is unlikely the G-Man is human; he has displayed supernatural abilities and speaks in a disturbing, irregular manner. Speculation surrounding the G-Man is varied, due to the mystery of his intentions and background. <br/> <br/><h3>The Name <br/></h3>The G-Man (short for "Government Man")  is not mentioned by name in any of the games; he is just referred to as the G-Man by the community since the data files containing his character model and texture were labelled "gman" when the original <a data-ref-id="3030-2980" href="/half-life/3030-2980/" slug="half-life">                                Half-Life</a> came out.<br/><br/><h3>Abilities <br/></h3>The G-Man seems to possess the ability to affect <a data-ref-id="3035-50" href="/space/3035-50/" slug="space">                               space</a> and time in an unknown capacity. However it is indicated several times across the Half-Life series that he is keeping his power in check due to certain "restrictions" placed upon him by his employers or associates. There is evidence to suggest that the G-Man is an advanced trans-dimensional being, as his powers over physical and spatial reality seem to be fairly significant. He seems able to move freely through time and space, is impervious to all known weapons, and can assert a form of mind control over humans.<br/><br/><h3>Actions <br/></h3>Throughout the Half-Life series, the G-Man takes several influential actions that directly affect the course of history within the Half-Life universe. Aside from having drastic consequences, these actions are also a display of his influence over time and space. The G-Man:<br/><br/><ul class="plain-list"><li>Initially provided <a data-ref-id="3005-639" href="/eli-vance/3005-639/" slug="eli-vance">                                Dr. Eli Vance</a> with the crystal sample, taken from the <a data-ref-id="3005-648" href="/the-nihilanth/3005-648/" slug="the-nihilanth">                                Nihilanth's</a> chamber in the <a data-ref-id="3035-75" href="/xen/3035-75/" slug="xen">                                Xen</a> border world, which initiated the <a data-ref-id="3015-66" href="/resonance-cascade/3015-66/" slug="resonance-cascade">                                resonance cascade</a> that devastated the <a data-ref-id="3035-64" href="/black-mesa-research-facility/3035-64/" slug="black-mesa-research-facility">                                Black Mesa facility</a> and subsequently alerted the <a data-ref-id="3015-64" href="/the-combine/3015-64/" slug="the-combine">                                Combine </a>to Earth's existence in the first game.</li> <li>Responsible for detonating a nuclear warhead at <a data-ref-id="3035-64" href="/black-mesa-research-facility/3035-64/" slug="black-mesa-research-facility">                                Black Mesa</a> which destroyed the facility at the end of the expansion pack  <a data-ref-id="3030-16508" href="/half-life-opposing-force/3030-16508/" slug="half-life-opposing-force">                                Half-Life: Opposing Force</a>.</li><li>When HECU Marine Corporal <a data-ref-id="3005-992" href="/adrian-shephard/3005-992/" slug="adrian-shephard"> Adrian Shephard</a> unexpectedly survived the incident, the G-Man placed him in some kind of otherworldly "storage" so that he would not interfere with the events that were to come. <br/></li> <li>Saved the life of Dr. Vance's daughter <a data-ref-id="3005-640" href="/alyx-vance/3005-640/" slug="alyx-vance">                                Alyx Vance</a> during the Black Mesa Incident.<br/> </li> <li>Used his powers over space-time to place <a data-ref-id="3005-341" href="/gordon-freeman/3005-341/" slug="gordon-freeman">                                Gordon Freeman</a> into temporal stasis, waking him some twenty years later, during the  Combine occupation of Earth. In the interim, Gordon was unaware of events occurring on Earth and did not age. </li> <li>Planted a hypnotic suggestion in the mind of <a data-ref-id="3005-640" href="/alyx-vance/3005-640/" slug="alyx-vance">                                Alyx Vance</a> which was later activated at the G-Man's will. </li> </ul> <br/><h2>Trademarks</h2><figure data-align="right" data-embed-type="image" data-img-src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/1/13692/901491-c1a3d0000.jpg" data-ref-id="1300-901491" data-resize-url="" data-resized="" data-size="small"><a href="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/1/13692/901491-c1a3d0000.jpg" data-ref-id="1300-901491"><img src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_small/1/13692/901491-c1a3d0000.jpg"></a><figcaption>G-Man passing by</figcaption></figure> Though he appears as an average suit-wearing Caucasian male, the G-Man displays behaviours and physical characteristics that belie his otherworldly origin. Among them are:<br/><br/><ul class="plain-list"><li><b>A bizarre manner of speech.</b> The G-Man speaks with a halting, irregular cadence that places emphasis on unusual syllables and stretches out certain words. He also speaks with an occasional lisp; in particular, his elongated "S" sounds vaguely recall the reptilian manner of a snake's hiss. Later on in the series, his awkward demeanour becomes less and less prominent, in favor of a slightly more "human" personality.</li> <li><b>Always around the corner.</b> Throughout <a data-ref-id="3030-2980" href="/half-life/3030-2980/" slug="half-life">                                Half-Life</a> and its sequel, the G-Man can frequently be seen observing Gordon's progress from an often unreachable vantage point. He always seems to appear in the unlikeliest places and at the most unusual times, adding to the mystique of his unknown nature.</li> </ul> <ul class="plain-list"><li><b>His outfit.</b> Taking the two episodes out of the equation, the G-man always carries his suitcase and the obligatory inexpensive-looking blue suit.</li><li><b>Fidgeting.</b> The G-Man's most prominent "fidget" is how he has a compulsion to occasionally adjust and readjust his necktie. He does this vigorously when the Vortigaunts take Gordon out of the G-Man's clutches at the beginning of Episode One.</li> </ul><br/><h2>Monologues</h2><br/> <h3>Half-Life</h3><blockquote><h3><figure data-align="right" data-embed-type="image" data-img-src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/1/13692/901495-c5a10000.jpg" data-ref-id="1300-901495" data-resize-url="" data-resized="" data-size="small"><a href="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/1/13692/901495-c5a10000.jpg" data-ref-id="1300-901495"><img src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_small/1/13692/901495-c5a10000.jpg"></a><figcaption>End-game monologue in Half-Life</figcaption></figure></h3> <i><a data-ref-id="3005-341" href="/gordon-freeman/3005-341/" slug="gordon-freeman"> </a></i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> <a data-ref-id="3005-341" href="/gordon-freeman/3005-341/" slug="gordon-freeman"> </a></i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i>Gordon Freeman in the flesh... or rather in the <a data-ref-id="3055-30" href="/hev-suit/3055-30/" slug="hev-suit"> </a>        Hazard Suit.<br/>I took the liberty of relieving you of your weapons... most of them were government property. As for the suit... I think you've earned it.<br/><br/>The border world, <a data-ref-id="3035-75" href="/xen/3035-75/" slug="xen"> </a><a data-ref-id="3035-75" href="/xen/3035-75/" slug="xen">           Xen</a>, is in our control for the time being, thanks to you.<br/>Quite a nasty piece of work you've managed over there, I am impressed.<br/><br/>That's why I'm here Mr. Freeman. I have recommended your services to my... eh... employers, and they have authorized me to offer you a job. They agree with me that you have limitless potential.<br/><br/>You've proved yourself a decisive man, so I don't expect you'll have any trouble deciding what to do. If you're interested, just step into the portal and I will take that as a yes. Otherwise, well... I can offer you a battle you have no chance of winning... rather an anti-climax after what you just survived.<br/><br/>[Tram Door opens] <br/>Time to choose.<br/><br/>[Stepping through the portal] <br/>Wisely done Mr. Freeman! I will see you up ahead.<br/><br/>[Standing still] <br/>Well it looks like we won't be working together. No regrets, Mr. Freeman.<br/>[G-Man hereafter teleports the player to a room full of enemies.]<br/></blockquote><br/><br/><h3>Half-Life: Opposing Force</h3><blockquote><figure data-align="right" data-embed-type="image" data-img-src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/1/13692/906561-gmanasasas.jpg" data-ref-id="1300-906561" data-resize-url="" data-resized="" data-size="small"><a href="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/1/13692/906561-gmanasasas.jpg" data-ref-id="1300-906561"><img src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_small/1/13692/906561-gmanasasas.jpg"></a><figcaption>G-Man talking to Adrian Shephard</figcaption></figure>So <a data-ref-id="3005-992" href="/adrian-shephard/3005-992/" slug="adrian-shephard"> </a> <a data-ref-id="3005-992" href="/adrian-shephard/3005-992/" slug="adrian-shephard"> </a>   Corporal Shephard, we meet at last.<br/><br/>Please don't think that I've been avoiding you - a great many matters required my attention in these... troubled times. I do hope you understand, and now I require a further indulgence on your part; I can not close my report until every loose end has been tied up. The biggest embarrassment has been <a data-ref-id="3035-64" href="/black-mesa-research-facility/3035-64/" slug="black-mesa-research-facility">              Black Mesa Facility</a>, but I think that's finally taken care of itself. Quite so...<br/><br/>But there is still a lingering matter of witnesses. I admit I have a fascination with those who adept and survive against all odds. They rather remind me of myself. If for no other reason, I argued to preserve you for a time.<br/><br/>While I believe a civil servant like yourself understand the importance of... discretion, my employers are not quite so trusting, and rather than continually subject you to the irresistible human temptation of telling all, we have decided to... convey you somewhere you can do no possible harm, and where no harm can come to you.<br/><br/>I'm sure you can imagine there are worse alternatives.<br/></blockquote><br/><br/><h3>Half-Life 2 - Start Sequence</h3><blockquote><h3><figure data-align="right" data-embed-type="image" data-img-src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/0/1379/178135-750px_halflife2_gman_prologue.jpg" data-ref-id="1300-178135" data-resize-url="" data-resized="" data-size="small"><a href="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/0/1379/178135-750px_halflife2_gman_prologue.jpg" data-ref-id="1300-178135"><img src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_small/0/1379/178135-750px_halflife2_gman_prologue.jpg"></a><figcaption>The G-man in the intro of Half-Life 2</figcaption></figure></h3>Rise and shine, <a data-ref-id="3005-341" href="/gordon-freeman/3005-341/" slug="gordon-freeman"> </a> <a data-ref-id="3005-341" href="/gordon-freeman/3005-341/" slug="gordon-freeman"> </a>  Mr. Freeman. Rise and shine. <br/>Not that I wish to imply that you have been sleeping on the job. No one is more deserving of a rest, and all the effort in the world would have gone to waste until... well, let's just say your hour has come again.<br/><br/>The right man in the wrong place can make all the difference in the world.<br/>So wake up Mr. Freeman... wake up and smell the ashes. </blockquote><br/><br/><h3>Half-Life 2 - End Sequence</h3><blockquote><p>Time, <a data-ref-id="3005-341" href="/gordon-freeman/3005-341/" slug="gordon-freeman"> </a>           Dr. Freeman? Is it really that time again?<br/>It seems as if you only just arrived. You've done a great deal in a small timespan. You've done so well, in fact, that I've received some interesting offers for your services. Ordinarily, I wouldn't contemplate them, but these are extraordinary times. <br/><br/>Rather than offer you the illusion of free choice, I will take the the liberty of choosing for you... if and when your time comes round again. I do apologize for what must seem to you an arbitrary imposition, Dr. Freeman. I trust it will all make sense to you in the course of... well... I'm really not at the liberty to say.<br/><br/>In the meantime...<br/>This is where I get off.</p></blockquote><br/><br/><h3>Half-Life 2: Episode One</h3><blockquote><p>[Entering a doorway only to realize he's being blocked off by <a data-ref-id="3015-221" href="/vortigaunt/3015-221/" slug="vortigaunt"> </a> Vortigaunts.]<br/>We'll see... about that!</p></blockquote><br/><br/><h3>Half-Life 2: Episode Two</h3> <i><a data-ref-id="3005-341" href="/gordon-freeman/3005-341/" slug="gordon-freeman"> </a></i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><i> </i><br/><blockquote><h3><figure data-align="right" data-embed-type="image" data-img-src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/0/24/10751-Gman-Flashback-HL2Ep2.jpg" data-ref-id="1300-10751" data-resize-url="" data-resized="" data-size="small"><a href="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/0/24/10751-Gman-Flashback-HL2Ep2.jpg" data-ref-id="1300-10751"><img src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_small/0/24/10751-Gman-Flashback-HL2Ep2.jpg"></a><figcaption>Heart-to-heart with Gordon</figcaption></figure></h3> <p>Doctor Freeeemaaan?<br/>I realize this moment may not be the most convenient for a heart-to-heart, but I had to wait until your... <a data-ref-id="3015-221" href="/vortigaunt/3015-221/" slug="vortigaunt"> </a>               friends [chuckles] were otherwise occupied. <br/><br/>There was a time they cared nothing for <a data-ref-id="3005-640" href="/alyx-vance/3005-640/" slug="alyx-vance"> </a>        Ms. Vance, when their only experience of humanity was a crowbar coming at them down a steel corridor. When I plucked her from <a data-ref-id="3035-64" href="/black-mesa-research-facility/3035-64/" slug="black-mesa-research-facility">              Black Mesa</a> [chuckles], I acted in the face of objections that she was a mere child and of no practical use to anyone. I have learned to ignore such nay-sayers, when... quelling them... was out of the question.<br/><br/>Still, I am not one to squander my investments, and I remain confident she was worth far more than the initial... appraisal. That's why I must now extract from you some small repayment owed for your own survival.<br/><br/></p><figure data-align="right" data-embed-type="image" data-img-src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/0/2433/293851-ep2_outland_020021.jpg" data-ref-id="1300-293851" data-resize-url="" data-resized="" data-size="small"><a href="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/0/2433/293851-ep2_outland_020021.jpg" data-ref-id="1300-293851"><img src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_small/0/2433/293851-ep2_outland_020021.jpg"></a><figcaption>Prepare for unforeseen consequences.</figcaption></figure> See her safely to <a data-ref-id="3035-121" href="/white-forest/3035-121/" slug="white-forest"> </a>           White Forest, Dr. Freeman. I wish I could do more than keep an eye on you, but I have agreed to abide by certain... restrictions.<br/><br/>[Talking to <a data-ref-id="3005-640" href="/alyx-vance/3005-640/" slug="alyx-vance"> </a> Alyx]<br/>Well... now listen carefully my dear.<br/>When you see your... <a data-ref-id="3005-639" href="/eli-vance/3005-639/" slug="eli-vance"> </a>               father, relay these words: "Prepare for unforeseen consequences."  </blockquote> <br/><h2>Trivia</h2><ul class="plain-list"><li><figure data-align="right" data-embed-type="image" data-img-src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/1/13692/1201157-gmancase.png" data-ref-id="1300-1201157" data-resize-url="" data-resized="" data-size="small"><a href="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/1/13692/1201157-gmancase.png" data-ref-id="1300-1201157"><img src="http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_small/1/13692/1201157-gmancase.png"></a><figcaption> Inside the G-Man's briefcase in Half-Life 1 </figcaption></figure> In the first <a data-ref-id="3030-2980" href="/half-life/3030-2980/" slug="half-life">               Half-Life</a>, it was possible to look inside G-Man's briefcase by using the <a data-ref-id="3015-4088" href="/developer-console/3015-4088/" slug="developer-console">            console</a> command noclip or viewing the texture manually. The briefcase appear to contain a pistol, some documents and a computer of some sort. The two textures can be seen to the right. It can be assumed that at one point in development, the briefcase was meant to be opened at some point in the storyline. There are no such textures in Half-Life 2.<br/></li><li>When looking through the source code for the G-Man in Half-Life 2, this developer comment can be found at the top of the file:  </li></ul><blockquote><p>"The G-Man, misunderstood servant of the people"   <br/></p></blockquote><ul class="plain-list"><li>The G-Man is voiced by <a data-ref-id="3040-48873" href="/michael-shapiro/3040-48873/" slug="michael-shapiro">         Michael Shapiro</a>; the same voice actor as <a data-ref-id="3005-642" href="/barney-calhoun/3005-642/" slug="barney-calhoun">  Barney Calhoun</a>.<br/></li></ul>]]></description><gender>1</gender><id>421</id><image><icon_url><![CDATA[http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/square_avatar/0/30/11508-gman.jpg]]></icon_url><medium_url><![CDATA[http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_medium/0/30/11508-gman.jpg]]></medium_url><screen_url><![CDATA[http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/screen_medium/0/30/11508-gman.jpg]]></screen_url><small_url><![CDATA[http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_small/0/30/11508-gman.jpg]]></small_url><super_url><![CDATA[http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_large/0/30/11508-gman.jpg]]></super_url><thumb_url><![CDATA[http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/scale_avatar/0/30/11508-gman.jpg]]></thumb_url><tiny_url><![CDATA[http://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/square_mini/0/30/11508-gman.jpg]]></tiny_url></image><last_name/><name><![CDATA[G-Man]]></name><real_name><![CDATA[Unknown]]></real_name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/g-man/3005-421/]]></site_detail_url><first_appeared_in_game><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/game/3030-2980/]]></api_detail_url><id>2980</id><name><![CDATA[Half-Life]]></name></first_appeared_in_game><concepts><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-66/]]></api_detail_url><id>66</id><name><![CDATA[Resonance Cascade]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/resonance-cascade/3015-66/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-8/]]></api_detail_url><id>8</id><name><![CDATA[Teleportation]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/teleportation/3015-8/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-1566/]]></api_detail_url><id>1566</id><name><![CDATA[Mysterious Ally]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/mysterious-ally/3015-1566/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-1413/]]></api_detail_url><id>1413</id><name><![CDATA[Voice Acting]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/voice-acting/3015-1413/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-1796/]]></api_detail_url><id>1796</id><name><![CDATA[Foreshadowing]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/foreshadowing/3015-1796/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-485/]]></api_detail_url><id>485</id><name><![CDATA[Black Mesa]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/black-mesa/3015-485/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-863/]]></api_detail_url><id>863</id><name><![CDATA[Interactive Cutscene]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/interactive-cutscene/3015-863/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-2226/]]></api_detail_url><id>2226</id><name><![CDATA[Unusual Speech Patterns]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/unusual-speech-patterns/3015-2226/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-2261/]]></api_detail_url><id>2261</id><name><![CDATA[Pseudonym]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/pseudonym/3015-2261/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-2906/]]></api_detail_url><id>2906</id><name><![CDATA[Agents]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/agents/3015-2906/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-1396/]]></api_detail_url><id>1396</id><name><![CDATA[Recurring Character]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/recurring-character/3015-1396/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-2218/]]></api_detail_url><id>2218</id><name><![CDATA[Unreliable Mentor]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/unreliable-mentor/3015-2218/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-1014/]]></api_detail_url><id>1014</id><name><![CDATA[Cameo Appearance]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/cameo-appearance/3015-1014/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-64/]]></api_detail_url><id>64</id><name><![CDATA[The Combine]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/the-combine/3015-64/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-2561/]]></api_detail_url><id>2561</id><name><![CDATA[Betrayal]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/betrayal/3015-2561/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-1276/]]></api_detail_url><id>1276</id><name><![CDATA[Machinima]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/machinima/3015-1276/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-27/]]></api_detail_url><id>27</id><name><![CDATA[Multiple Endings]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/multiple-endings/3015-27/]]></site_detail_url></concept><concept><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/concept/3015-5581/]]></api_detail_url><id>5581</id><name><![CDATA[Slow In-Game Introduction]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/slow-in-game-introduction/3015-5581/]]></site_detail_url></concept></concepts><enemies><enemy><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/enemy/3005-737/]]></api_detail_url><id>737</id><name><![CDATA[Dog]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/dog/3005-737/]]></site_detail_url></enemy><enemy><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/enemy/3005-642/]]></api_detail_url><id>642</id><name><![CDATA[Barney Calhoun]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/barney-calhoun/3005-642/]]></site_detail_url></enemy><enemy><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/enemy/3005-640/]]></api_detail_url><id>640</id><name><![CDATA[Alyx Vance]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/alyx-vance/3005-640/]]></site_detail_url></enemy><enemy><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/enemy/3005-992/]]></api_detail_url><id>992</id><name><![CDATA[Adrian Shephard]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/adrian-shephard/3005-992/]]></site_detail_url></enemy><enemy><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/enemy/3005-639/]]></api_detail_url><id>639</id><name><![CDATA[Eli Vance]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/eli-vance/3005-639/]]></site_detail_url></enemy><enemy><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/enemy/3005-341/]]></api_detail_url><id>341</id><name><![CDATA[Gordon Freeman]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/gordon-freeman/3005-341/]]></site_detail_url></enemy></enemies><franchises><franchise><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/franchise/3025-293/]]></api_detail_url><id>293</id><name><![CDATA[Half-Life]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/half-life/3025-293/]]></site_detail_url></franchise><franchise><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/franchise/3025-588/]]></api_detail_url><id>588</id><name><![CDATA[Portal]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/portal/3025-588/]]></site_detail_url></franchise></franchises><friends/><games><game><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/game/3030-16508/]]></api_detail_url><id>16508</id><name><![CDATA[Half-Life: Opposing Force]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/half-life-opposing-force/3030-16508/]]></site_detail_url></game><game><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/game/3030-7814/]]></api_detail_url><id>7814</id><name><![CDATA[Half-Life: Blue Shift]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/half-life-blue-shift/3030-7814/]]></site_detail_url></game><game><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/game/3030-1539/]]></api_detail_url><id>1539</id><name><![CDATA[Half-Life 2]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/half-life-2/3030-1539/]]></site_detail_url></game><game><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/game/3030-14328/]]></api_detail_url><id>14328</id><name><![CDATA[Half-Life 2: Episode One]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/half-life-2-episode-one/3030-14328/]]></site_detail_url></game><game><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/game/3030-9480/]]></api_detail_url><id>9480</id><name><![CDATA[Half-Life 2: Episode Two]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/half-life-2-episode-two/3030-9480/]]></site_detail_url></game><game><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/game/3030-12896/]]></api_detail_url><id>12896</id><name><![CDATA[Half-Life: Uplink]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/half-life-uplink/3030-12896/]]></site_detail_url></game><game><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/game/3030-17729/]]></api_detail_url><id>17729</id><name><![CDATA[The Orange Box]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/the-orange-box/3030-17729/]]></site_detail_url></game><game><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/game/3030-22690/]]></api_detail_url><id>22690</id><name><![CDATA[Half-Life: Decay]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/half-life-decay/3030-22690/]]></site_detail_url></game><game><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/game/3030-22721/]]></api_detail_url><id>22721</id><name><![CDATA[Half Life 2: Survivor]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/half-life-2-survivor/3030-22721/]]></site_detail_url></game><game><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/game/3030-25640/]]></api_detail_url><id>25640</id><name><![CDATA[Synergy]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/synergy/3030-25640/]]></site_detail_url></game><game><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/game/3030-31910/]]></api_detail_url><id>31910</id><name><![CDATA[Half-Life Deathmatch: Source]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/half-life-deathmatch-source/3030-31910/]]></site_detail_url></game><game><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/game/3030-39814/]]></api_detail_url><id>39814</id><name><![CDATA[Black Mesa]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/black-mesa/3030-39814/]]></site_detail_url></game><game><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/game/3030-2980/]]></api_detail_url><id>2980</id><name><![CDATA[Half-Life]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/half-life/3030-2980/]]></site_detail_url></game></games><locations><location><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/location/3035-64/]]></api_detail_url><id>64</id><name><![CDATA[Black Mesa Research Facility]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/black-mesa-research-facility/3035-64/]]></site_detail_url></location><location><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/location/3035-63/]]></api_detail_url><id>63</id><name><![CDATA[City 17]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/city-17/3035-63/]]></site_detail_url></location><location><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/location/3035-75/]]></api_detail_url><id>75</id><name><![CDATA[Xen]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/xen/3035-75/]]></site_detail_url></location><location><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/location/3035-332/]]></api_detail_url><id>332</id><name><![CDATA[gm_construct]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/gm_construct/3035-332/]]></site_detail_url></location><location><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/location/3035-1994/]]></api_detail_url><id>1994</id><name><![CDATA[New Mexico]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/new-mexico/3035-1994/]]></site_detail_url></location><location><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/location/3035-121/]]></api_detail_url><id>121</id><name><![CDATA[White Forest]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/white-forest/3035-121/]]></site_detail_url></location><location><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/location/3035-731/]]></api_detail_url><id>731</id><name><![CDATA[Combine Citadel]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/combine-citadel/3035-731/]]></site_detail_url></location></locations><objects><object><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/object/3055-72/]]></api_detail_url><id>72</id><name><![CDATA[Briefcase]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/briefcase/3055-72/]]></site_detail_url></object><object><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/object/3055-3062/]]></api_detail_url><id>3062</id><name><![CDATA[Necktie]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/necktie/3055-3062/]]></site_detail_url></object><object><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/object/3055-3686/]]></api_detail_url><id>3686</id><name><![CDATA[Suit and Tie]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/suit-and-tie/3055-3686/]]></site_detail_url></object></objects><people><person><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/person/3040-4498/]]></api_detail_url><id>4498</id><name><![CDATA[Gabe Newell]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/gabe-newell/3040-4498/]]></site_detail_url></person><person><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/person/3040-4493/]]></api_detail_url><id>4493</id><name><![CDATA[Doug Lombardi]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/doug-lombardi/3040-4493/]]></site_detail_url></person><person><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/person/3040-48873/]]></api_detail_url><id>48873</id><name><![CDATA[Michael Shapiro]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/michael-shapiro/3040-48873/]]></site_detail_url></person><person><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/person/3040-4467/]]></api_detail_url><id>4467</id><name><![CDATA[Ken Birdwell]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/ken-birdwell/3040-4467/]]></site_detail_url></person></people><platforms><platform><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/platform/3045-94/]]></api_detail_url><id>94</id><name><![CDATA[PC]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/pc/3045-94/]]></site_detail_url></platform><platform><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/platform/3045-19/]]></api_detail_url><id>19</id><name><![CDATA[PlayStation 2]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/playstation-2/3045-19/]]></site_detail_url></platform><platform><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/platform/3045-84/]]></api_detail_url><id>84</id><name><![CDATA[Arcade]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/arcade/3045-84/]]></site_detail_url></platform><platform><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/platform/3045-32/]]></api_detail_url><id>32</id><name><![CDATA[Xbox]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/xbox/3045-32/]]></site_detail_url></platform><platform><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/platform/3045-17/]]></api_detail_url><id>17</id><name><![CDATA[Mac]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/mac/3045-17/]]></site_detail_url></platform><platform><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/platform/3045-86/]]></api_detail_url><id>86</id><name><![CDATA[Xbox Live Marketplace]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/xbox-live-marketplace/3045-86/]]></site_detail_url></platform><platform><api_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/api/platform/3045-35/]]></api_detail_url><id>35</id><name><![CDATA[PlayStation 3]]></name><site_detail_url><![CDATA[http://www.giantbomb.com/playstation-3/3045-35/]]></site_detail_url></platform></platforms></results><version>1.0</version></response>
